dillons.com 2012-12-03

# Dillons

**The Kroger Co. Privacy Policy**

The Kroger Co. recognizes that privacy is very important to our customers, and we pledge to protect the security and privacy of any personal information customers provide to us. This includes customers' names, addresses, telephone numbers, e-mail addresses, credit card and checking account information, and any information that can be linked to an individual. Kroger collects and securely stores this personal information.

As part of our commitment to our customers, Kroger has implemented the following comprehensive privacy policy.

**Kroger will protect and preserve customer privacy.**

As one of America's largest retail grocery companies, and one of the nation's largest pharmacy operators, Kroger serves millions of customers every day. We value our customers' trust and we promise to safeguard the personal information that they share with us through purchases in our stores and online; the use of Shopper's Cards, personal checks, credit and debit cards; entries in Kroger promotions; and visits to our retail pharmacies and websites. 

**Kroger carefully safeguards its customers' pharmacy records.**

We have special procedures that protect your pharmacy records. For detailed information on our pharmacy privacy policy, see the Pharmacy Privacy Notice, which conforms to the guidelines established under the federal law known as the Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act (HIPAA).

**Kroger is especially sensitive to children's use of the Internet.**

Our website is family friendly. We follow all the guidelines established under the federal law known as the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act.

Kroger does not actively seek personal information about children under 13 years of age without permission from their parent or legal guardian. We do not provide personal information about children to any third-party except in accordance with other sections of this privacy policy and the Pharmacy Privacy Notice.

If you are a parent or guardian of a child under the age of 13 and believe he or she has disclosed personally identifiable information to us, please contact us. A parent or guardian of a child under the age of 13 may review and request deletion of the child's personally identifiable information and prohibit its use

**Customers have control of their personal information.**

Kroger will not release personal information about customers without their permission, except as required by law or legal process (including pursuant to court orders, subpoenas, interrogatories, or similar directive carrying the force of the law), or as set forth below. 

It is your choice to provide Kroger with your personally identifiable information. By signing up for a Shopper's Card or using our website, customers agree to allow Kroger to contact them by various means about promotions (for example, by mail or e-mail), certain recalls (for example, by telephone, e-mail or cash register receipt), and other information of interest. Customers who do not wish to be contacted may notify us at any time either in writing, by telephone or in person at one of our stores. Customers on the "do not contact" list will not receive offers for savings by mail/e-mail, will be excluded from Kroger general mailing lists, will not be automatically entered in sweepstakes by using a Shopper's Card, and may not receive certain legal notices. Kroger and its affiliates may use personal customer information to create merchandising and promotional programs tailored around specific purchases, the frequency of store visits, volume of purchases, and other data. Kroger also may use the data it collects to investigate and respond to customer requests, concerns, and claims.

**We do not sell, trade or rent our customers' personal information to outside companies or marketing firms, except in connection with the sale of a pharmacy, in connection with Kroger's loss prevention efforts, or as described in this privacy policy.**

Kroger may utilize the services of third-party loss prevention specialists for assistance in cases of suspected fraud or theft, and—in connection with such loss prevention activities—may disclose personal information as we deem necessary or appropriate without restriction. We may share personal customer information with our subsidiaries, affiliates, agents, representatives and trusted business partners for the limited purpose of providing services or information to Kroger or our customers at our direction. We may provide third parties with certain information that is necessary to fulfill an order you have placed with us, such as providing your name and address to a shipping carrier for delivery or passing on your credit card information to a credit card processor when you pay by credit card. We require our agents and business partners to hold customer information provided by Kroger in strict confidence, except as specifically set forth in this policy. We are not responsible for any additional information that you provide directly to these third parties. 

The company collects, stores, and uses aggregate data that do not contain personally identifiable information, such as demographic or statistical information. This aggregate data may be shared with and used by third parties to help us and our suppliers better serve and understand our customers. 

**Kroger does not collect personally identifiable information through passive methods that are hidden from the customer, except as described below.**

When you visit our websites, we may use web beacons (a small graphic), or you will be assigned a permanent "cookie" (a small, unique identifier text file) to be stored on your computer's hard drive. The purpose of this technology is to identify you when you visit our site so we can enhance and customize your online experience. Further, we may offer certain features that are only available through the use of this technology. 

Cookies are required for us to provide optimal use of our website and for customers to access certain portions of our website, including but not limited to: logging in, purchasing items, participating in promotions, and using certain website services. You are always free to refuse cookies if your browser settings permit. You may also manually delete cookies from your computer.

We also collect certain technical information from your computer each time you request a page during a visit to our websites. This information may include your Internet Protocol (IP) address, your computer's operating system, browser type and the address of a referring website, if any. We collect this information to enhance your experience during your visit to our site and for system administration, security and troubleshooting purposes. 

Kroger may use third-party software to serve ads on its websites, implement e-mail marketing campaigns, and manage other interactive marketing initiatives.  Further, Kroger may contract with third parties to serve ads on third-party websites in order to optimize advertising campaigns. This third-party software may use cookies, web beacons, or similar technology to help manage and optimize your online experience with us. 

**We enforce strict security measures to prevent unauthorized access to, disclosure of or use of customers' personal information.**

Employees who violate the Company's customer privacy safeguards are subject to disciplinary action up to and including termination. 

When you enter personal information online, that information is encrypted using a security protection called Secure Sockets Layer so that information you provide to us is encrypted during transmission over the Internet. 

We strive to collect, use and disclose personal information consistent with the laws of the United States as well as the laws of other countries in which we do business, including the laws of the European Union. For detailed information on our privacy policy with respect to the European Union, please see our E.U. Safe Harbor Privacy Policy. 

**We are not responsible for the content or the privacy and security policies and practices of any third-party websites accessible from a link on our websites.**

Throughout our websites, we provide links to third-party websites, which may or may not be co-branded, in order to provide additional goods, services or information to our customers. Any personal information or Kroger-specific information (such as Shopper's Card number) that you provide when accessing a third party website is subject to that third party's privacy policy. Kroger is not responsible for information you provide directly to a third party. If you register for or use such third party websites, both Kroger and the third party may receive information collected in conjunction with the use of the websites as described in the privacy policy on those websites. 

**We welcome your comments and questions.**

Customers may access their own readily available and easily retrievable purchasing information upon written request. Customers may request changes to their personal information by providing written notification to us by mail, in person at one of our stores, or via their online account. In all cases, customers must furnish proof of identity in order to make changes. 

As changes occur in Kroger's business, technology and the law, we will continue to review and revise this policy. The use of information we gather now is subject to the privacy policy in effect at the time of use. We may send you periodic notices of changes to our policy, unless you have instructed us not to contact you, but you should check our website periodically to see the current policy. We will attempt to provide our customers with notice of material changes to this policy by regularly scheduled mailings, cash register receipt messages, e-mail or other means. 

If you have any questions or concerns, please contact one of our customer representatives at 1-866-221-4141; e-mail us through the Customer Comment section of our website or write us at: 

Customer Relations  
The Kroger Co.  
1014 Vine Street  
Cincinnati, OH 45202  

This privacy policy was posted and is effective as of July 10, 2009. We reserve the right to change our privacy policy at any time. You can always view the current Privacy Policy by clicking on the Privacy Policy link at the bottom of any page of [OwensMarket.com](http://www.owensmarket.com/) . 

## The Kroger family of stores includes:

---|---|---|---
